Life is kind of like a plain canvas.
生活就像一张平坦的帆布
What you put on the canvas is up to you.
在上面放什么都取决于你自己
And I know that you're gonna create your own masterpiece.
我知道你准备创造自己的杰作
Our stories are what makes us unique.
我们的故事让我们变得独一无二
They are like fingerprints and snowflakes, and the stars in the milkyway.
他们就像指纹和雪花  还有银河中的星星
None of them are the same.
每个都与众不同
You, me, all of us are story tellers by nature.
你  我  我们所有人都是天生的故事家
Sharing our stories makes us human,
分享故事会让我们变得更加人性化
and connects us to each other.
并让我们彼此紧密相连
It helps us to realize we're not alone on this crazy big planet we call home.
它让我们明白  在这个我们叫做家的疯狂大星球上  我们并不孤独
And so, my dear dreamer,
所以  我亲爱的梦想家
keep shooting for the stars.
为梦想继续努力
Believe in yourself.
相信自己
Because you were made from the universe.
因为你是宇宙的产物